File: FAQ

Why Assembly and not x/y/z ?:

	Why not, next question please.

Why i386 and not x64/ARM/RISC-V/<insert random shit> ?:

	I want to target my old computers. I never throw an old machine and I try to repair them when they are broken. 

Why another Operating System ?:

	I take drugs. 💊 Most of the code parts for this project were written 
	while I was on <acid at https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/LSD>.

In my opinion you should....:

	I don't care. 💅

I'm a transphobic piece of shit can I use your software ?:

	Well, technically I can't stop you from using it. But  I agree: you are a 
	piece of shit.

...:

	Boot Up or Shut Up!
